I know what the clue is.
Wait a minute.
Where did you get that?
The evidence room.
Did you put in a request?
No.
Go on.
I don't get it.
What's the use of these two cups?
The existence of these two cups itself
is problematic.
I read the trace evidence report.
Both have been used
and have the victim's fingerprints.
Under what circumstances would someone
pour a second cup of tea
when the first one still has tea in it?
My guess is
Mu Weijie went back to his room to take medicine
because he felt unwell.
But when he picked up the teacup,
he suddenly remembered that tea would affect the medicine's efficacy.
So he put down the cup
and got up to pour another glass of water.
So I presume he needed to take medicine that day,
which is why he used two cups.
And the medicine he took
might be the key to solving the case.
Stop.
Lin Rongrong said
that Mu Weijie died after they had sex.
Then he didn't take medicine for his heart condition.
Then what medicine did he take?
Sildenafil.
It's really possible.
The medicine Cheng Mo mentioned is called sildenafil,
commonly known as Viagra.
Theophylline and tannins in tea
will affect the efficacy of Viagra.
And an overdose of Viagra will overload the heart.
People with a history of heart disease are more prone to sudden heart failure.
Judging from my investigation of the scene at that time,
the victim's symptoms did look like he had taken Viagra.
He was physically weak,
and he took Viagra to drug a female student.
What a beast.
Captain Zhuang.
But this is just our speculation, right?
I didn't find any evidence at the scene.
Judging from the placement of the teacup,
the medicine
is here.
As expected.
There really is this medicine.
Shao.
I want a detailed autopsy report now.
This...
I'll take the blame for any problems.
We are one step closer to the truth.
Zhuang Lan.
You know Mu Weijie's situation very well.
A social celebrity, an art master.
He has a lot of influence.
The Investigation Bureau takes this case very seriously.
The public also needs a clear explanation.
Now the killer has confessed.
The logical chain of manslaughter is very clear.
Lin Rongrong's sabotage has been fully investigated.
The demands from all sides have been met.
We can totally close the case.
But why are you performing
an autopsy at this time?
Chief.
Public pressure,
social impact, demands from all sides,
I understand all of it.
But aren't we police?
I think the only demand I need to meet
is the truth itself.
The pill in Mu Weijie's body
and the physiological reaction it caused
will directly affect a young man's future.
Do you know that?
What you're saying is just an inference.
It is a fact that he broke in with a weapon,
smashed things, and caused the victim's death.
But your accident investigation team finally closed the case,
proving that
there is evidence behind the accident,
only to turn around and prove it was an accident.
It has caused such a huge public uproar.
What if
the autopsy results are different from what you expected?
Who will take responsibility?
I will.
Chief Sang.
I don't care about brilliant public opinion manipulation
or political tactics.
But my father only taught me one thing.
A police officer's duty is to speak for the dead
and protect the rights of the living.
As long as I haven't found any clues,
no matter where they are,
I will definitely dig them out.
You are just like your dad.
In a word...
Go.
In-situ observation of the heart.
Clear fluid in the pericardial cavity.
Now preparing to extract the heart
to weigh it.
How is it, Shao?
Cause of death confirmed.
He did take an overdose of aphrodisiacs,
which caused sudden death.
In his stomach,
a high concentration of sildenafil was found.
About the dosage of five pills.
The normal recommended dose
is 20 to 30 milligrams,
which is about half a pill.
Five pills reached 250 milligrams,
which is ten times the recommended dose.
Ten times?
Did he need such a large dose?
It's not impossible.
It involves male ego.
I have handled similar cases before.
Do you think someone could have
concentrated all the medicine together
and forced it down his throat?
That's unlikely.
First, at the scene,
we didn't find any trace of forced feeding.
Second, even if he was forced,
it would require a violent conflict
to cause a heart attack.
So I think
he probably took it before having sex
voluntarily.
That means,
it was an accident after all.
A perverted teacher wanted to rape a female student,
took an overdose of aphrodisiacs,
triggered a heart attack and died.
Allen was unlucky
to just run into it.
Yes.
The process was complicated,
but the conclusion is simple.
You've all worked hard recently.
No matter what,
our efforts were not in vain.
Fang,
go prepare the documents to close the case.
Okay.
Be careful on your way back.
Rongrong.
Xiaoyue.
Officer Zhuang.
The case has been clearly investigated.
Mu Weijie died from an overdose of sildenafil,
which led to heart failure.
Although
Lin Rongrong broke the law by destroying the crime scene,
considering she is a victim,
I have already applied
for her to be released on bail.
You can go back now.
Thank you, Officer Zhuang.
However...
Don't run around when you get back.
I may contact you at any time.
Okay.
Bye, Officer Zhuang.
Have you been okay these past few days?
I'm fine.
Why did you come to see me so late?
That doesn't make sense.
He even knows that tea neutralizes the drug's effects.
Where exactly did it go wrong?
Mr. Cheng.
The case is closed.
Don't overthink it.
You haven't eaten, right?
I have some bread here.
Eat some bread
to fill your stomach.
No, thanks.
Just have one piece.
I really don't want any.
Thanks.
If you won't eat it, I will.
Can't you eat less?
Only one piece?
Who said they wanted to lose weight?
Sis.
One piece it is.
Do you think someone could
concentrate all the drugs together
and then force them down?
We can't close the case.
Fang Deyan.
What's wrong, Mr. Cheng? Why are you in such a hurry?
Listen to me first.
Don't submit it yet.
I mean the case closure report.
Why aren't we submitting it again?
We have new findings.
Let's wait a bit longer.
New findings?
Why don't I know about this?
You'll know later.
Also,
could you do me a favor?
Do you a favor?
Tell me, what is it?
Are you sure?
Okay.
Come on.
Right.
This is what I've always told them.
The duty of the police is to speak for the dead
and protect the rights of the living.
Right.
As long as
this clue is not clear yet,
no matter where it is,
we must dig deep.
We can't just stop because there's resistance.
Exactly.
Right.
The autopsy results
will completely affect a young man's future.
Exactly.
What about the family?
Okay.
Thanks.
Thank you. Okay, thanks.
It's handled.
Good thing you found it in time
to rule out Allen as a suspect.
Go ahead.
Don't worry about the family.
You are the best, Chief.
My idol. You really are my idol.
Cut it out.
Just save me some trouble in the future.
Okay, I know.
I will definitely save you some trouble.
But um,
please take a look at this first.
This is the case closure report you mentioned, right?
Then I must read it carefully.
This is the application to continue the investigation.
Please have a look first. Take your time.
Take your time.